>> Brian Holt: 在开始请求使用 API 之前，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Before we get
to requesting against the API,
我想告诉你怎么处理那些叫做习惯挂钩的东西
I wanna show you how to do with
something that's called a custom hook.
所以现在我们都在这个地方使用过使用状态
So right now we've just been using
useState all over the place, but
如果你注意到动物的 HTML 或者这个动物和品种
if you notice HTML for animal, or
this one here right animal and breed.
这几乎是一样的，对，就像这样，
These are almost the same thing,
right, to the point that like,
如果我们能有一点可以重复使用的话就好了
it'd be nice if we could have
some sort of like reusable bit.
这就像是我们的下拉菜单
That would do like a drop-down for us, and
我们不需要做这首歌和环境
we didn't have to do all this song and
circumstance.
我们可以把它们保持在一起，所以我们还是去做吧。
And we could maintain them together,
so let's actually go do that.
因此，请在此处创建新文件，并将其称为 useDropdown.js。
So make a new file here,
and call it useDropdown.js.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，在此，您想从 "反应"中导入 React 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
here you wanna import React from 'react'.
> > Brian Holt: 我们还会使用 useState。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
we're also gonna use useState.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，然后我要说康斯特 useDropdown，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
then I'm gonna say const useDropdown,
这就是我们要创造的钩子
this is gonna be our hook
that we're gonna create.
它会被标记为某种默认状态
And it's gonna take in a label,
some sort of default state,
还有一些可供选择的选项清单
and some sort of a list of
options to put in there.
>> Brian Holt: 然后在底部，我们将导出缺省 useDropdown。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then down at the bottom
we're going to export default useDropdown.
所以我们要说康斯特州
So we're gonna say const state,
useState, so
我们就像个一般的下拉菜单
we're gonna make this
like a generic dropdown.
>> Brian Holt: 因此不是使用状态，但是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So not useState but
setState >> Brian Holt: Equals useState ，以及
setState
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Equals useState, and
缺省状态将为它们传入的任何状态，因此缺省状态为 " 缺省状态 " 。
the default state of this is going to be
whatever they pass in, so default state.
>> Brian Holt: 我们会获得某种身份标识，因此您只需要
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're gonna get some
sort of ID, so you just need it to be
一些独特的东西，因为我们要给东西钥匙，
something unique, because we have
to give things keys and such.
所以我要用模板的绳子所以我要用背叉
So I'm gonna use template strings,
so I'm gonna use backticks,
backticks 是键盘上的旁边的 1 。
backticks are the ones next
to 1 on your keyboard.
然后我们会说用下去的花括号
Then we'll say use-drop
down-$ curly braces and
那么 JavaScript 表达式可以在此处进行。
then JavaScript expressions
can go in here.
所以我想说的是 label.replace
So, I'm gonna say, label.replace, so
将任何空格从字符串中取出，并使其为小写。
take any spaces out of the string and
also make it lowercase.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，如果此处的标签类似于 Best Dogs ，那么
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So like if label here
was something like Best Dogs Ever or
那样的东西对吧
something like that, right?
这会让这个 > > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
What this would do is it would make this
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Look like that,
对，这就是这里的产出，对吧 ?
right, that's what this
would output there, right?
不管它是否可读，都是独一无二的事情。
Doesn't matter that it's readable,
it just matters that it's unique.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，然后我们将调用的组件
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and then the
component that we're gonna make is called
a Dropdown，因此 const Dropdown 等于一个箭头函数。
a Dropdown, so
const Dropdown equals an arrow function.
我们要用那个隐式的回报
And we're just gonna use that
implicit return again with
圆括号，等号 htmlFor 等于标识。
the parentheses,
equals label htmlFor equals the ID.
>> Brian Holt: 然后在这里，这会有一个 ID，我们需要贴上标签
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then here, this is
gonna have an ID, we need to put a label
这里的标签是从参数中进来的
inside of that label which is
coming in here from the parameters.
然后我们把它放进去
And then we're gonna put
a select inside of that.
>> Brian Holt: 我们也要给它选择一个 ID ，所以 id = [id]，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we have to give that
select an ID as well, so id= [id],
值 = 我们在此处创建的状态，因此状态。
value = state which we created up here,
so state.
>> Brian Holt: OnChange，我们将呼叫 e 和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: OnChange,
we're going to call e and
我们要把 setState 设置为 e.target.value。
we're gonna say to setState
to be e.target.value.
然后模糊的同一件事，翁布卢
And then the same thing for blur, onBlur.
> > Brian Holt: 然后我们还得给它禁用的东西，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we have to
give it that disabled thing as well,
禁用等于 options.length 三重 = 0。
disabled equals options.length triple = 0.
我们要给它一个选项，那就是没有价值，对吧 ?
Here we're gonna give it an option of all,
which is gonna have no value, right?
这意味着什么时候一切都不会有任何选择
Which means it's going to have
nothing selective when it's on all.
然后我们就会说 " options.map " ，用地图做同样的事。
And then here we're gonna say options.map
and do the same thing with map.
这将是一些选项中的某个项目，我们将继续使用项目。
So this is gonna be some item in the array
of some option, we'll stick with item.
使用带括号的隐式返回和
Use our implicit return
with parentheses and
表示选项键=[item]， value=[item]，
say option key=[item], value=[item],
然后就在那儿了
and then item right there as well.
>> Brian Holt: 请让我的括号完全匹配，然后开始。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Get my parentheses
all matched up, here we go.
>> Brian Holt: 现在我们有一个通用的下拉组件，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now we have this
generic drop down component, right?
这将会成为一个标签，一些默认的状态选项和
That's gonna take in a label,
some default state options and
make 一个下拉组件。
make a dropdown component.
所以现在我们要在下面回到这里
So now what we're going to
return down here at the bottom,
我们要归还国家的" 下拉"
is we're gonna return the state,
the Dropdown.
然后我们也会返回这个设定状态的功能。
And then we're also gonna return
this setState function as well.
> > Brian Holt: 就像这样，现在我们就像用了一个钩子一样，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Like that, and now we
can use this just like we used a hook,
因为这会给我们国家的
because this is gonna give us the state.
Dropdown会处理所有状态的设置和取消状态，对吧 ?
The Dropdown's gonna handle all of the
setting and unsetting of the state, right?
然后，在稍后的情况下，我们将返回此 setState 函数。
And then just in case as well for later,
we're gonna return this setState function.
因此，除了使用 Dropdown之外，我们还可以以编程方式对其进行更新。
So that we can programmatically update it,
in addition to using the Dropdown.
所以我知道这有点抽象
So I understand this is a little abstract,
我们已经把动物 Dropdown 和繁殖的 Dropdown 都带走了
we've taken the animal Dropdown and
the breed Dropdown.
然后我们就把它变成了这种一般的 Dropdown hook。
And then we've just formed it into
this kind of generic Dropdown hook.
>> Brian Holt: 到目前为止还好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Good so far?
好吧那我们就去找搜索程序吧
All right, so let's go ahead and
go back to the search params.
> > Brian Holt: 我们要做的，不是做动物和 setAnimal，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And what we're gonna do,
instead of doing animal and setAnimal,
我们要做的是我们会说 const.
what we're gonna do is
we're gonna say const.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 首先你要把上面的东西进口
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: First thing is
you have to import up top,
因此，请从 ./useDropdown 中导入 useDropown 。
so Import useDropown from ./useDropdown.
我们还需要养狗我们就能追踪到
We still need breeds so
we'll keep track of that,
但现在我们要做的就是
but now what we're gonna do is we're gonna
说 const [动物，动物下拉 ] 。
say const [animal, animalDropdown].
我们现在就把它放在那个位置
And we'll actually just
leave it at that for now,
= 使用 DropDown ，我们将给动物贴上标签。
= useDropDown, and
we'll give it Animals the label.
> > Brian Holt: 我们会把它作为默认状态，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We'll give it
dog as the default state,
我们会把动物作为选择的选项清单
and we'll give it Animals as
a list of options to choose from.
然后我们会说 const， >> Brian Holt: Breed，
Then for breeds we're gonna say const,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Breed,
BreedDropdown 我们把它留给我们
BreedDropdown and
we'll leave it at that for
现在等于 useDropdown 和 "Breed"
now equals useDropdown with "Breed"
空字符串作为缺省状态，是吗 ?
empty string as a default state, right?
然后，我们会从 API 中重新处理这一问题，这只是第二次。
And breeds which again we'll handle this
from the API here is just a second later.
所以现在我把这只动物下拉下来了
So now I have this animal Dropdown and
this breed drop down, so
而不是把所有这些标签都用在这里
rather than having all of this
label stuff here for that.
我要删除动物我要删除 Breed
I'm gonna delete Animal and
I'm gonna delete Breed.
>> Brian Holt: 所以现在我就有一个位置不同，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now I just have
the location one, which is different,
我们现在不想做那种普通的
we don't wanna make
that generic right now.
但最酷的是我有一个动画部和一个 BreedDropdown。
But what's cool is I just have
an AnimalDropdown and a BreedDropdown.
> > Brian Holt: 我认为这很酷，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
that's pretty cool in my opinion,
我们已经把这个逻辑取出来了我们把它引出来了
we've kinda taken out this logic, we
extracted it out to this useDropdown hook.
现在我们把这些小动画公司
And now we just get these
little AnimalDropdown,
BreedDropddown ，自我包含的下拉列表。
BreedDropddown, self contained dropdowns.
所以如果我救了这个
So if I save this and
我回到自己的代码，这一切都和现在一样。
I go back over to my code this all
works exactly the same way now.
但它使用的是这种共享的通用类，或者类似的钩子。
But it's using this kind of shared
generic class, or hook, as it were.
>> Brian Holt: 现在我可以写各种各样的单元
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And what's great about
this is now I can write all sorts of unit
测试我可以把这些都用在这里
tests,and I can use this
all over the place.
我可以向我的未来保证这是一个非常好的作品
And I can kinda guarantee to my future
self that this is a really good piece of
可以反复重复使用的代码。
code that I can reuse over and
over and over again.
>> Brian Holt: 现在我们有一大堆关于未使用的变量的错误，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now we have a bunch
of errors around unused variables,
我们会暂时解决的但你应该现在就知道了
we will fix this momentarily, but
you should expect to see that right now.